

1800 102 2558 | +91 9818882211





Supriya Mohanta Reatured 7





Senior Software Engineer seeking roles in Application Support, Production Support, Application Maintenance, Incident Management, Change Management, Shell Scripting, Oracle, GIT, Jenkins, Teamcity, Unix, Putty, SQL Developer, Note ++, Winscp, Jira, Service Now



Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Notice Period: 3 Months

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E.

[Electronics/Telecommunication]

Current Designation: Senior Software Engineer- Application

Support

Current Company: HCL Technologies Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore. Chennai. Pune Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: System Analyst

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services Marital Status: Single/unmarried

 $\label{thm:continuous} \textit{Key Skills: Senior Software Engineer, System Analyst, Application Support, Production Support, Production Support, Application Support, Production Support, Pro$ Maintenance, Incident Management, Change Management, Shell Scripting, Oracle, GIT, Teamcity, Unix, Putty, SQL

Developer, Note ++, Winscp, Jira, Service Now, Udeploy, Jenkins

Verified : Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 18-Jan-21 Last Modified: 18-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

Having 3+years of IT experience in L2 level of Application / Production Support Proficient in UNIX commands Good knowledge of SHELL SCRIPTING Proficient in ORACLE Knowledge in DEVOPS TOOLS(GIT, JENKINS, TEAMCITY)

Extensive experience in Application & Production Support and Maintenance

Having experience in Telecom Domain and Banking Domain.

Proactively working on resolving issues before they impact on business

Communicating with client regarding the impact of issues and resolving with in SLA Wisely managing known errors / issues in a consistent manner

Work Experience

HCL Technologies as Senior Software Engineer- Application Support May 2018 to Dec 2020

2) Project name: Citi Group Global Market Production Support

Duration: May -2018 to till date

Client: Citi Bank Team size: 18

Business domain: Banking Environment: Unix, Sql

Tools used: SQL Developer, Putty and Project based tools like Autosys,

ITRS Geneos, Udeploy, Teamcity, Service Now

Devops tools: Git, Jenkins, Teamcity

Role: Application / Production support engineer

Applications: PRIMO, GCE, XSTREAM, ZTS, MOGA, KDB

Project Description:

Citi Global Markets Production Support manages various FO, MO, CRD& Razor applications to ensure uninterrupted running of the whole IT production application. It is the first level support for developers and tester to implement their patch changes and code implementation. Deployment of various application also performed to ensure the environment is running fine, also flow from front office to middle office flow also goes fine. In addition to the daily checklist tasks to ensure application availability this team is responsible for all front office to middle office will be fine, along with that access to user for various application,

Server migration, server reboot, Deployment of all application, Any Issue regarding environment. All in out team is responsible to run environment smoothly.

The Senior Analyst / Analyst position provides support to the firms consulting operations in the execution and delivery of investment consulting services to external clients. The individual will primarily be responsible for the coordination and



Important

· Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

completion of analytical work including client presentations, for a variety of regional offices around the globe.

ROLES & RESPONISIBILTY:

Responsible for providing the support in L1&L2 level depending on the priority of the issues

Handling user request on Both Production & Access control mailbox, Ad hock Activities

Preparing EOD reports of all regions. Checking log flow across various application.

Enhancing the checks before the market opens and automating various reports to the users.

Configure log file monitoring for Central Trade Reporting System which receives a copy of trade from different source systems

Source, prepare and analyze investment fund related information, using Mcrosoft Excel and proprietary software

Configure ITRS Geneos tool for development and support applications

Prepare Daily SOD reports for jobs, Processes and tasks and send to the user without fail

Prepare Manager Search Reports, proactively communicating with multiple teams to resolve the issues

Prepare Quarterly Monitoring Reports

Prepare Research packs for Global Investment Management manager meetings

Proactively solve users query within a time period and update the ticket accordingly

Proficiency with Mcrosoft PowerPoint application, ability to prepare client presentations

Liaise with investment managers and collect information on their offerings

HCL Technologies as Senior Software Engineer- Application Support May 2018 to Till Date

working as senior software engineer with HCL

Harman as Software Engineer

Dec 2016 to May 2018

PROJECT DETAILS:

1) Project name: MP MOBILE, SERBIA

Duration: Dec-2016 to May-2018

Team size: 6

Business domain: Telecom

Environment: Unix, Oracle 10g

Tools used: Putty, Sql developer, Note ++, Winscp , Jira, Uc4

Role: Application / Production support engineer

DESCRIPTION:

Vip mobile is a Serbian mobile network operator and a member of the Telekom Austria Group based in Belgrade. It is the exclusive strategic partner of Vodafone in Serbia

BRIAN was introduced in 1998 by Betty Kainz, Michael Reindl and Gabriela Hansal. The first application was an interface to the Post-billing system . Now BRIAN is serving more than 200 interfaces (commands) from its Gateway systems

It is a web service interface to the backend systems (HLR, ABC, IN, VMS etc). Historically, it serves as an Interface to Amdocs billing system. It also acts as an interface for web applications (Network Admin, eCare, Partner Web, cost manager etc) to fulfill backend request. As an interface to the system, the services for this server to use is XML.

ROLES & RESPONSIBIL TY:

The Connectivity Services & Operation team supports following application & systems.

BRIAN modules, Cmds And Brian Gateway

LDAP provisioning system

MOBILE NUMBER portability
AMDOCS online applications "Csm", PORT-IN Management

AUTOMATION scripts

UC4 customization & issues

Customer Complaints

Production fixes

BILLING related customer data issues

Production to Testing server data copy Server health check and monitoring

Arrange SWAT call during high priority issues
Resolve issues related tickets based on the priority

Escalate to L3 whenever needed by mails or Tickets

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E (Electronics/Telecommunication) from Biju Patnaik University of Technology (BPUT) in 2014

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

| Skill Name | Version Last Used Experience |
|--|------------------------------|
| Oracle | |
| Shell Scripting | |
| GIT | |
| Jenkins, Teamcity | |
| Unix | |
| SQL DEVELOPER | |
| Winscp, Jira, Uc4 | |
| ************************************** | |

Languages Known

| Language | Proficiency | Read | Write | Speak |
|----------|-------------|------|-------|-------|
| English | Expert | ✓ | ✓ | ✓ |
| Hindi | Proficient | ✓ | ✓ | ✓ |
| Oriya | Expert | ✓ | ✓ | ✓ |

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: **General**Physically Challenged: **No**

Job Type: Permanent
Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.